habbo.com.sg 2006-12-31

# Habbo ~ Privacy Policy

Here at Habbo Hotel we want everyone to have a good time. Also, we promise to keep your hotel as secure and as private as we can. The hotel is a place for you to hang out in and meet new people. We have a few rules that you do need to accept before you can become a member, so you need to read the Privacy Policy all the way through before you can join. 

By clicking the 'accept' button when you register, you will be agreeing to us holding and processing your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you are under 14 we think you should check with your parents or guardians to see if they are happy for you to be a member of Habbo Hotel. Please get them to explain any areas of this statement you may not fully understand. 

If you have any concerns regarding your personal information, website content, or any queries with regard to Habbo Hotel practices please contact us. 

**YOUR CONSENT**

The Internet is a global environment and involves the transmission of data internationally. By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this policy will be reflected here. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We collect personal information when you use our website, including your completion of online forms (such as the registration form), your participation in contests and surveys, your subscription for certain newsletters and Enhanced Services, your posting of messages to the Message Boards and Chat Services, and your emails or other communications with us. We also collect “cookie” information automatically about your visit to our Website. 

**PURPOSES OF COLLECTION**

We process personal information about you for the purposes of: 

  * Understanding your needs and improving our offering of information, products and services to you, such as special discounts and deals. 
  * Enabling you to send your Habbo Friends emails and SMS without them knowing your contact details. 
  * Administering your account with us and letting you know about things we are doing that might affect you (eg changes to Sulake Singapore’s Pte Ltd's procedures, changes to the Terms and Conditions, etc). 
  * Carrying out research (ie scientific, social, economic and market). 
  * Maintaining information as a reference tool or general resource. 
  * Providing you with personalised information about products and services. 

**CHAT ROOMS AND MESSAGE BOARDS**

We make chat facilities and message boards available to you. Please remember that any information you choose to disclose in these areas may become public information. We would encourage you to exercise caution when deciding to disclose information, and be careful what you reveal to people you don't yet know. Please refer to our Terms and Conditions. 

**OPTING OUT, UPDATE OR CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION**

If you do not wish to receive the hotel's newsletter, or information about products and services supplied by Sulake Singapore Pte Ltd or third parties, do not tick the boxes at the bottom of the registration form. You may change these options anytime by selecting the 'Update your Habbo ID' link within the game in the Hotel view. 

Alternatively, you may opt out by emailing us. 

**SECURITY**

All information you provide us with, and all information contained in your account, is encrypted. This coding lets your browser automatically encrypt or scramble data before you send it to us. Transactions will not be permitted if your browser does not accept the encryption. Only authorised personnel of Sulake Singapore Pte Ltd or its partners can decode this information and such personnel will only do so in accordance with our, or their, privacy policy. We employ this facility to ensure that all information we receive from you is in a secure environment at all times. 

**CHILDREN**

Habbo Hotel is not intended for use by children, especially those under the age of 14. No one under the age of 14 is allowed to provide any personal information or to use our public discussion areas without parental consent. 

If your children disclose information about themselves in our public discussion areas, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, it is up to you to ensure they abide by our Terms and Conditions, caution them not to share personal information, and to monitor their use of the Website. 

If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our sites, we encourage you to email us. 

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. 

We use cookies to identify you when you visit us and to keep track of where you go so we can build up a demographic profile and learn about what suits you. 

Our use of cookies also allows the registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the Website and have access to information to their account. 

**DISCLOSURES**

We will not sell, share, or rent your information to others except as set out in this Privacy Policy. 

  * We will only disclose personal information to other companies within our group of companies and any third party whom we engage to process data on our behalf. We may also disclose this information to a Licensed Credit Reference Agency. 
  * The business partners, strategic partners, purchasers of our business and suppliers may gather information for their own purposes and for that reason we cannot exercise control over the uses to which they apply your personal information. It is, however, our belief that when we supply your details to them, they will keep your details secure and not pass them on to third parties and only use your details to market their own products to you. 
  * In the event of the sale of the Company or its assets your personal details may be disclosed to the purchaser of the Company or the purchaser of its assets. 
  * In the event that the Company is required to disclose any information by law, or by any stock exchange or governmental or regulatory authority having jurisdiction over the Company, the Company may disclose such information that is so required. 

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES**

Please be aware our Website may have advertisements and links to websites and services that may collect personal information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices and policies of these third parties. We encourage you to read the policies of all sites you use, as their policies may be materially different from ours.
